Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Smith Papers, 1887-1976; 3; 62 document boxes, 2 oversized boxes, and 3 oversized folders.
  - Correspondence, 1914-1975; 1
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 5), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 5), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 5), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 5), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 11), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 11), 1945 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 11), 1945 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 11), 1945 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (11 of 11), 1945 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 8), 1946 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 5), 1947 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 5), 1947 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 5), 1947 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 5), 1947 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 5), 1947 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 8), 1948 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 8), 1948 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 8), 1948 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 8), 1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 8), 1948 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 8), 1948 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 8), 1948 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 8), 1948 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 6), 1949 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 6), 1949 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 6), 1949 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 6), 1949 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 6), 1949 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 6), 1949 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1950 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1950 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1951 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1951 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1951 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1952 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1952 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1952 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1952 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 9), 1953 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1954 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1954 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1955 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1956 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 4), 1958 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 4), 1958 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 4), 1958 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 4), 1958 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1959 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1959 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1963 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1963 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1963 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 6), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 6), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 6), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 6), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 6), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 6), 1969 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 6), 1970 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 6), 1970 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 6), 1970 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 6), 1970 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 6), 1970 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 6), 1970 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 8), 1971 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1973-1975 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1953-1973 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (1 of 11), undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (2 of 11), undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (3 of 11), undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (4 of 11), undated (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (5 of 11), undated (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (6 of 11), undated (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (7 of 11), undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (8 of 11), undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (9 of 11), undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (10 of 11), undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith (11 of 11), undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1939-1941 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1941-1942 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1942-1945 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1945 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1946-1951 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1951-1955 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1955-1961 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1961-1965 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1966-1968 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Telegrams: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Literary Productions, 1887-1976; 2
    The literary productions in this subseries were primarily produced by the Smith family and include address books and lists of addresses, diaries, and biographical information. The subseries includes material produced by Harley Smith, including his sermon notes, memo books, and materials from his time in the Student Army Training Corps.
    - Biographical Materials: Harley Smith, 1913, 1916, 1940-1948, 1962-1968 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Biographical Materials: Alice Bagby Smith, 1943-1969 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Biographical Materials: Wedding of Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1922 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Materials: 50th Wedding Anniversary of Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Materials: Weddings of Helen Frances Smith Hillman and Jimmye Standard Hillman, and William F. Cooper and Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, 1947, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Biographical Materials: Funeral of Alice Bagby Smith: (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Materials: Funeral of Alice Bagby Smith: (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Biographical Materials: Funeral of Harley Smith, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Biographical Materials: Certificates, 1919, 1929, 1940, 1947, 1966, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Materials: Certificates and Diplomas, 1888-1964, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Materials: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith 40 Years as Missionaries in Brazil, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Biographical Materials: Medical Records and X-Rays, 1966-1967 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Biographical Materials: Passports, 1923, 1933, 1943, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Biographical Materials: Passports, 1931, 1952, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Materials: Photographic Mats, undated (Box 128 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1932-1933 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1934-1937 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith: Loose Materials, 1934-1937 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1944 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1945-1947 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1971-1973 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Diaries: Alice Bagby Smith, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Diaries: Harley Smith, 1931, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Addresses: General, 1953, 1970-1971, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Addresses: General: (1 of 7), undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Addresses: General: (2 of 7), undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Addresses: General: (3 of 7), undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Addresses: General: (4 of 7), undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Addresses: General: (5 of 7), undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Addresses: General: (6 of 7), undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Addresses: General: (7 of 7), undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Addresses: Alabama-Montana, circa 1930-1970 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Addresses: New Mexico-Wisconsin, circa 1930-1960 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Addresses: Texas: A-K: (1 of 2), circa 1930-1970 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Addresses: Texas: A-K: (2 of 2), circa 1930-1970 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Addresses: Texas: L-Z, circa 1930-1970 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Addresses: Brazil: (1 of 3), undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Addresses: Brazil: (2 of 3), undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Addresses: Brazil: (3 of 3), undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Addresses: Brazil and Other Countries, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Addresses: Foreign Countries, circa 1930-1960 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Sermon Notes, 1924-1926, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Sermon Notes, 1926-1929, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Sermon Notes, 1929, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Sermon Notes, 1931-1933, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Sermon Notes, 1938, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Sermon Notes, circa 1939-1940, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Sermon Notes, 1941-1943, 1966, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Sermon Notes, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Sermon Notes: (1 of 2), 1946, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Sermon Notes: (2 of 2), 1946, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Sermon Notes, 1946-1964 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Sermon Notes, circa 1950-1965 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Sermon Notes, circa 1951, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Sermon Notes, 1957-1960 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Sermon Notes, 1958-1960 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Sermon Notes, circa 1963-1968 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Sermon Notes, 1966-1967, undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Sermon Notes, 1968-1971, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Sermon Notes: (1 of 15), undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Sermon Notes: (2 of 15), undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Sermon Notes: (3 of 15), undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Sermon Notes: (4 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Sermon Notes: (5 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Sermon Notes: (6 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Sermon Notes: (7 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Sermon Notes: (8 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Sermon Notes: (9 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Sermon Notes: (10 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Sermon Notes: (11 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Sermon Notes: (12 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Sermon Notes: (13 of 15), undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Sermon Notes: (14 of 15), undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Sermon Notes: (15 of 15), undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Memo Books, 1918, 1920-1921, 1924, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Memo Books, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Memo Books, 1947-1966 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Memo Books, 1948-1968 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Memo Books: (1 of 2), 1951-1968 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Memo Books: (2 of 2), 1951-1968 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Memo Books, 1953-1954 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Memo Books, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Memo Books, 1963-1965 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Memo Books, 1965-1969 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Memo Books, 1967-1969 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Memo Books, 1968-1969 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Memo Books, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Memo Books, 1970-1971, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Memo Books, 1971-1973 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Memo Books, 1972, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Memo Books: Mission Directory, 1955, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Memo Books: Sermon Notes, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Memo Books: Birthdays, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Memo Books: Portuguese, 1949-1951, 1954-1962 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Memo Books: Portuguese, 1959, 1962-1964 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Memo Books: Portuguese, 1957-1965 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Memo Books: Portuguese, 1966-1967 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Notes, circa 1920s-1970s (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Notes: (1 of 3), circa 1930s-1970s (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Notes: (2 of 3), circa 1930s-1970s (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Notes: (3 of 3), circa 1930s-1970s (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Notes, circa 1940-1965 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Notes, circa 1940s-1970s (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Notes, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Notes, 1966-1972 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Notes, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Unpublished Materials: Alice Bagby Smith and Helen Frances Smith, 1932, 1939, 1941-1942, 1955, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith, 1920, 1940-1942, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith, 1921, 1940-1942, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith, 1929, 1934, 1940, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith, 1939-1944, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith, 1940, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith: (1 of 2), 1942, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith: (2 of 2), 1942, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Unpublished Materials: Harley Smith, 1940-1948, 1954-1961, 1964, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Published Materials, 1932-1934, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Published Materials, 1956-1957 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Seminary Course, 1935, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Music: (1 of 2), undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Music: (2 of 2), undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Library Listing, 1942, 1973, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Student Army Training Corps: (1 of 3), 1918 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Student Army Training Corps: (2 of 3), 1918 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Student Army Training Corps: (3 of 3), 1918 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - World War I Military Insignia of Harley Smith, circa 1914-1918 (Box 128 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Programs, 1932-1953 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1919, 1934, 1944, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Books: Primeira Convencao Baptista Latino-Americana, by T. B. Stover, 1930 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Books: New Testament [Douay Version]: Belonged to Harley Smith, 1918 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Book, “Mary’s Meadow”, 1886 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Book, “My Memory’s Bouquet”, 1933 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Notebooks, 1887, 1939, undated (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Autograph Books, 1933, 1953-1954 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - General: Authorization of Sponsorship of Students, 1968-1969 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - General: Building Plans, 1955, undated (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - General: Organizational Pins, 1920, 1931 (Box 128 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - General: Calling Cards of Alice Bagby Smith, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - General: Coins, 1928, 1939 (Box 128 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - General: Loose Material from the Bible of Alice Bagby Smith, 1919, 1933, undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - General: Stamps, 1912-1926 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - General: Who's Who in Latin America, undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - General, 1918, 1955, undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - General: Fortune Telling, undated (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Financial Documents, 1914-1973; 3
    The financial materials in this subseries include bills, receipts, statements, deposit slips and check stubs. Some of the items are connected to the Smiths' work as missionaries in Brazil. The bulk of their personal financial documents are in the sub-subseries Personal Expenditures.
    - Promissary Notes, circa 1931-1965, undated (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Contributions and Offerings, 1925, 1935-1945, 1963-1971, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Contributions and Offerings, 1926-1936 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Contributions and Offerings, 1938, 1942, 1949-1951, 1960-1961, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Deposit Slips and Check Stubs, 1937-1942, 1946, 1955-1963, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Deposit Slips and Check Stubs, 1940-1961, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Deposit Slips and Check Stubs, 1940-1946, 1958-1970, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Deposit Slips and Check Stubs, 1954-1955, 1962-1969, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1925-1966, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1926, 1941-1942, 1947, 1954, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1926, 1935-1946, 1953-1954, undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1926-1969, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1926, 1935-1946, 1953-1954, undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1926-1969, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1931, 1949-1952, undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, Circa 1933-1972, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, Circa 1936-1960, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1936-1968, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1937-1942, 1960, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1938-1943, 1947, 1951, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1938-1948, 1958, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1938-1962, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1939, 1943, 1950-1968, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1940-1942, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1940-1945, 1958, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1941-1950, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1942-1947, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1942, 1954-1957, 1961-1965, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)